PRIYA GOVIL

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

(514) 659-5472

□ priyagovil02@gmail.com

Pincourt, QC

SKILLS

C# & Java

JavaScript, HTML & CSS

SQL Server & SQLite

Application Development

Unit testing

Data structures & algorithms

WPF, Node.js, ASP.NET, GitHub, Jira

EDUCATION

Diploma of College Studies in Computer Science

John Abbott College 2019-2023

Honors:

Dean's List (Fall 2020 & Fall 2021)

Diploma of Secondary Studies

École secondaire du Chêne-Bleu

2014-2019

LANGUAGES

English

French

Hindi



PROFILE

A computer science student at John Abbott College with working experience and knowledge in various software. Possess strong teamwork and problem-solving skills with fluency in English and French. Keen to pursue a career in Computer Science, specifically in software development or game programming.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer (Intern)

SharkNinja

June 2022 - August 2022

- Developing a download feature from back to front-end that allows other employees to have access to information in a simple and fast manner.
- Handling data refresh to generate fresh data for production tasks.
- Managing time in order to complete various given tasks in an efficient and timely manner.
- Working in a team to problem solve and meet deadlines while gaining experience and developing teamwork and technical skills.

Meat Associate

Walmart Canada

July 2021 - June 2022

- Separating, sorting, and organizing different types of meat.
- Ensuring customer satisfaction by going above and beyond to meet client expectations.
- Offering suggestions based on customer's preferences to meet their needs
- Working in a fast-paced environment while making sure that all products are displayed well and stored safely.

PROJECTS

Home Budget Application

January 2022 - May 2022

- Developing a home budgeting application with various features allowing potential users to manage their finances.
- Acquiring technical skills by learning about the different development cycles through the agile workflow.

Inventory Management Application

August 2022 - December 2022

- Developing an inventory management application with WPF using
- Working in teams to further our communication skills.

C# to help potential users manage their inventory items.

PRIYA GOVIL

DÉVELOPPEUR DE LOGICIELS

CONTACT

(514) 659-5472

□ priyagovil02@gmail.com

Pincourt, QC

COMPÉTENCES

C# et Java

JavaScript, HTML et CSS

SQL Server et SQLite

Développement d'applications

Tests unitaires

Structures de données et algorithmes

WPF, Node.js, ASP.NET, GitHub, Jira

ÉDUCATION

Diplôme d'études collégiales en informatique

Cégep John Abbott 2019-2023

Honneurs:

Liste des doyens (Fall 2020 & Fall 2021)

Diplôme d'études secondaires

École secondaire du Chêne-Bleu

2014-2019

LANGUES

Anglais

Français

Hindi

Punjabi



PROFIL

Étudiant en informatique au Cégep John Abbott avec de l'expérience professionnelle et des connaissances dans divers logiciels. Possède de solides compétences en travail d'équipe et en résolution de problèmes. Désireux de poursuivre une carrière en informatique, en particulier dans le développement de logiciels ou la programmation de jeux.

EXPÉRIENCE PROFESSIONNELLE

Développeur de logiciels (Stagiaire)

SharkNinja

Juin 2022 - Août 2022

- Développer une fonctionnalité de téléchargement qui permet aux autres employés d'avoir accès aux informations de manière simple et rapide.
- Gestion de l'actualisation des données pour générer de nouvelles données qui sont utiliser pour les tâches de production.
- Gérer le temps afin d'accomplir diverses tâches de manière efficace et en temps opportun,
- Travailler en équipe pour résoudre des problèmes et respecter les délais tout en développant les compétences techniques et en acquérant de l'expérience.

Associée aux viandes

Walmart Canada

Juillet 2021 - Juin 2022

- Séparer, trier et organiser différents types de viande.
- Assurer la satisfaction de la clientèle en allant au-delà des attentes pour répondre aux demandes des clients.
- Offrir des suggestions basées sur les préférences des clients pour répondre à leurs besoins
- Travailler dans un environnement au rythme rapide tout en s'assurant que tous les produits sont bien présentés et stockés en toute sécurité.

PROJETS

Application pour le budget familial

Janvier 2022 - Mai 2022

- Développer une application de budgétisation à domicile avec diverses fonctionnalités permettant aux utilisateurs potentiels de gérer leurs finances.
- Acquérir des compétences techniques en apprenant les différents cycles de développement à travers le flux de travail agile.

Application de gestion de

Août 2022 - Décembre 2022

l'inventaire

- Développer une application de gestion de l'inventaire avec WPF en utilisant C# pour aider les utilisateurs potentiels à gérer leurs articles en stock.
- Travailler en équipe pour améliorer nos compétences en communication.